<!--Copyright 2015 Lexmark International, Inc. All rights reserved.--><Help xml:lang="en" dbid="v24160202"><Topic Id="7002">Conserve supplies by printing multiple pages per side of the paper.
</Topic><Topic Id="7003">Conserve supplies by printing on both sides of the paper.
</Topic><Topic Id="7113">“Two-sided printing” is not available because "Booklet" is selected in the "Advanced layout" menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7126">“Sheets per bundle” is not available because “Fold” is selected in the “Fold” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7103">“Booklet” is not available because an option other than “Use printer setting,” “Off,” or “Saddle stitching” is selected in the “Staple” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7104">“Booklet” is not available because an option other than “Use printer setting” or “Off” is selected in the “Hole punch” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7106">“Poster” is not available because an option other than “Use printer setting,” “Off,” or “Saddle stitching” is selected in the “Staple” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7107">“Poster” is not available because an option other than “Use printer setting” or “Off” is selected in the "Hole punch" menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7120">“Poster” is not available because an option other than “Off” is selected in the “Fold” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7122">“Booklet” is not available because “Fold individual pages” is selected in the “Fold” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7128">“Booklet” is not available because a “Trifold” option is selected in the “Fold” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7130">“Poster” is not available because a “Trifold” option is selected in the “Fold” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7135">“Booklet” is not available because “Add blank/preprinted front cover” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7136">“Pages per side” is not available because “Add blank/preprinted front cover” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7137">“Poster” is not available because “Add blank/preprinted front cover” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7138">“Booklet” is not available because “Add blank/preprinted back cover” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7139">“Pages per side” is not available because “Add blank/preprinted back cover” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7140">“Poster” is not available because “Add blank/preprinted back cover” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7141">“Booklet” is not available because “Use different paper for first printed page” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7142">“Pages per side” is not available because “Use different paper for first printed page” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7143">“Poster” is not available because “Use different paper for first printed page” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7144">“Booklet” is not available because “Use different paper for last printed page” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7145">“Pages per side” is not available because “Use different paper for last printed page” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7146">“Poster” is not available because “Use different paper for last printed page” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7201">The selected option is not recommended for use with envelope paper sizes. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7212">The selected option is not recommended for use with envelope paper sizes. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7206">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected paper type. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7211">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected paper type. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7208">"Maintain original page size” can be used only with the statement, letter, B5, A5, A4, and A6 paper sizes. Any other paper size selection may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7215">The selected option is not recommended for use as a booklet cover. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7216">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected “Document reading order” option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7217">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected “Document reading order” option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7218">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected “Document reading order” option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7219">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected “Document reading order” option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7220">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected “Binding edge” option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7221">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected “Binding edge” option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7222">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected “Presentation direction” option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7223">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected “Presentation direction” option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7150">“Booklet” is not available because “Add blank/preprinted covers” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7151">“Poster” is not available because “Add blank/preprinted covers” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7152">“Booklet” is not available because “Use different paper for first/last printed page” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7153">“Poster” is not available because “Use different paper for first/last printed page” is selected in the “Paper” section.
</Topic><Topic Id="7131">The “Automatic” option is not available because “Selected paper size” is selected in the “Output paper size” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7132">The “Selected paper size” option is not available because “Automatic” is selected in the “Scaling” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7133">This feature is not available because “Booklet” is selected in the “Advanced layout” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7134">This feature is not available because “Poster” is selected in the “Advanced layout” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7147">This feature is not available because an option other than one is selected in the “Pages per side” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7200">The selected option is not recommended for use with the "Booklet" option in the "Advanced layout" menu. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7202">The selected option is not recommended for use with the "Poster" option in the ”Advanced layout" menu. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7203">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected "Hole punch" option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7205">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected "Staple" option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7207">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected "Two‑sided printing" option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7209">The selected option is not recommended for use with the “Booklet” option in the “Advanced layout” menu. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7213">The selected option is not recommended for use with the selected “Fold” option. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7102">Some settings may be unavailable because "Booklet" is selected in the "Advanced layout" menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7112">“Hole punch” is not available because "Booklet" is selected in the "Advanced layout" menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7105">“Staple” is not available because "Poster" is selected in the "Advanced layout" menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7114">“Hole punch” is not available because "Poster" is selected in the "Advanced layout" menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7116">“Staple” is not available because “Fold individual pages” is selected in the “Fold” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7124">Some settings may be unavailable because “Fold” is selected in the “Fold” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7117">“Fold” is not available because an option other than ”Use printer setting,” “Off,” or “Saddle stitching” is selected in the “Staple” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7125">“Fold individual pages” is not available because “Saddle stitching” is selected in the “Staple” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7118">“Hole punch” is not available because an option other than “Off” is selected in the “Fold” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7119">“Fold” is not available because an option other than ”Use printer setting” or “Off” is selected in the “Hole punch” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7121">“Fold” is not available because “Poster” is selected in the “Advanced layout” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7123">“Fold individual pages” is not available because “Booklet” is selected in the “Advanced layout” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7127">“Staple” is not available because a “Trifold” option is selected in the “Fold” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7129">“Hole punch” is not available because a “Trifold” option is selected in the “Fold” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7148">“Trifold” options are not available because “Saddle stitching” is selected in the “Staple” menu.
</Topic><Topic Id="7204">The selected option is not recommended for use with the "Transparency" option in the "Paper type" menu. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7210">The selected option is not recommended for use with the "Transparency" option in the "Paper type" menu. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7214">The selected option is not recommended for use with the "Transparency" option in the "Paper type" menu. This setting may produce unexpected results or may cancel the print job.
</Topic><Topic Id="7001">Conserve supplies by decreasing the “Toner darkness” setting.
</Topic><Topic Id="7224">If you select a different watermark and apply the changes, then you may lose this watermark. Use the watermark manager to save this watermark.
</Topic></Help>